I want everyone to know that this this playground and this whole this entire facility was funded without resident tax dollars. It was all done through grants,
and, we have, senator Aramin here with us.
Angie was very helpful in in allowing us to get the additional funds to make sure that we could do everything that we wanted to do. So
we we we got a $500,000
steep grant, and we got a legislative appropriation from senator Raman. And I really appreciate everything he's done for the town. You know, as far as senators goes, he's done an incredible job compared to what we've had in the past. So I just want everybody to understand that. Yep. And it's important to have people that help us in Hartford. So thank you very much.
You.
Most important thing is to introduce the people that actually got this accomplished.
So I've learned the committee members, and I just want you to understand all the hard work that they put into it. No.
It. Yeah.
Grace Gestanian.
>> I can see her. Grace,
come on. You're
in the picture. You're in the picture.
>> Come on. Come on, Grace. Grace, we're in the picture. Grace,
>> Whoo. Alright? She's done all the hard work. She's dealt with all the contractors,
all the meetings, all the conversations.
>> Really, thank you very much. The the town of Andover is better for it. Alright? Thank you very much. Whoo. And you should have put your name on the list.
>> Alright. Thank
you for all coming on such a hot day. You're welcome. I want everybody
>> in here for the ribbon picture, if you don't mind. How's it going? Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey.
Hey.
Smile.
One more.